I'm sorry, but they only know about the opening when you're the master.
There's an opening.
I'll turn it off now.
Now?
Is this really a game?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Heh heh heh
Ah, beginner!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hi!
Hello!
For a second there, I thought it was an on-air accident.
There's no sound.
I don't know if there's any sound coming out.
So, this is Mariko, this week's part timer...
It's been a while... I mean, it's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mariko is the one who rules over all the men in the world.
She rules them all.
I'll tell you what.
I'll let you watch it on the air.
Why is that?
There's no reason why that's the case, not really.
So, I'm just saying.
The broadcast, uh, so, uh...
If you're watching the live broadcast, first of all...
As we mentioned last week
Devil in the House
event is coming up next year on Sunday, March 31st.
Sunday, March 31st
The route of the event!
It will be held at Kanagawa Kenmin Hall!
It's like a sacred place for us!
We really want you to come!
We really hope that you will come.
I've already told you about the VIPS seats.
As I mentioned before
The front line in front of the building.
You know, the terrain is amazing.
We are now selling seats in that area by advanced lottery.
If you're interested...
I'd like you to see it from the front.
If you're the kind of guy who wants to be dominated by Mariko...
Please come to the front.
We're waiting for you.
We'll accept your application until 23:59 on Monday, December 10th.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Speaking of Devil in the House...
For the event!
I've been working on it for a while.
For that.
On location.
I've been filming for it.
That's right, I did a little...
I did some stuff.
Various things.
What are you going to do?
I'm not sure yet.
I see.
I can't say.
I'm afraid I can't.
I'm sorry.
If you really want me to go, I'll tell you.
No, no, no, no, no...
That was fast.
I'd love to see that, too.
I think it's a very interesting picture.
I think it's very interesting from a picture point of view.
Yes, I think so.
Well, I hope you enjoy it.
Yes, that's right.
So that's what I thought.
Yes.
And speaking of location shooting...
At the end of this year
December 31st, right on New Year's Eve.
Yes, sir.
Devils coming and going...
We'll have a special program.
Yay!
We hope you'll watch it too.
Please do.
We've gone to a lot of trouble for this special.
Yes.
We went out of our way.
Yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
I wonder what this is...
I don't know.
Anyway, I was screaming a lot.
I was screaming a lot, wasn't I?
I was like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
You were, weren't you?
I was.
I felt like I was watching a sporting event.
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Or something like that.
Yes.
That's probably going to be a part of the "Come Devil, Come Devil" episode.
I think it'll be shown here and there.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, as for the content, I'll just say it's a bit of a sticking point, but...
That was fast.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's start with the program, shall we?
Okay.
I'd like to begin.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes!
That's why...
Well, well, well... it's Friday already!
So early!
Well, well, well...
By the way...
Today is the 16th of December?
The 15th.
By the way, tomorrow is Saturday.
They say tomorrow is Telephone Day.
The very first telephone was installed in Japan in 1890.
In 1890, the 23rd year of Meiji.
Tokyo and Yokohama had the first telephones in Japan.
Wow!
That's what I thought.
It started from there.
There have been many things since then, and now we have cell phones and so on.
Yes, about this much.
It's evolved so much.
It's just...
You know...
The calling rates back then...
Well...
Flat rate.
Yes.
40 yen, huh?
If you convert it to today's price...
If I make a phone call, it's about 240,000 yen.
What? Not once, I think.
I was so surprised. Install it.
After that, it was fine. 240,000 yen for one job is not good.
That's too expensive, no matter how much.
But it wasn't cheap at all.
In the old days, before cell phones came back... pay phones...
Phone cards...
You used to pay in cash, like this.
It cost 10 yen for 3 minutes in that neighborhood
That's right... that's right... that's right...
In the city, it's shorter.
That's what I was told.
I guess it wasn't that easy.
240,000 yen a time is not good.
That's not good.
Wow!
Wow, that's really amazing.
You know what day it is, and we talked about the old days, right?
Yeah, about the old days...
Evolution is really amazing, isn't it?
What is this? It's been a few hundred years.
It hasn't been that long.
That's why it's so scary.
We're living in 2023, right now.
100 years from now, for example...
It's going to be a terrible thing.
That's nice.
I can't see that world, but...
But you and us...
Just barely. If it's 100 years...
If it's 100 years, I'll be 125 years old.
123 years old.
That's so cool!
Mariko, you'll be like, "Happy 120th!
That's right. Wow! Amazing!
Amazing. I can't even imagine what's going on.
I can't even imagine. No, it's true.
I can't imagine what it was like back in the Showa era.
I remember when I was in the Showa period, I imagined the present...
The future...
Even in comic books...
They talk about how the cities of the future will be like this, but the only thing they've actually realized is cell phones.
Oh, I see.
In the year 2000, it was like cars were flying in the sky.
It's not flying yet, is it? Not yet.
In the 1970s, they said that in 30 years cars would be flying.
I see... And then, the antenna from the clock was extended like this...
Yes, sir
Hello? Cool!
Yes... a spy...
Spies.
The spy was doing this and saying, "Wow, what's that?
Yes.
It's even more amazing now.
Yes...
It's like we're all spies.
That's for sure.
We are.
I see.
Or maybe not so much.
Well, there are times when we go too far, aren't we?
Yes, yes, yes, we may have had enough of it.
Yes, that's right.
Can someone please tell me what will happen?
Please tell me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Come to my grave
Don't cry at my grave.
I'm not there.
I've heard that.
Yes, I have. There's a sense of urgency.
Let's hear your letter.
Let's hear from you.
What a timely topic!
We talked about mandarin oranges earlier.
Here it is.
Someone who went mandarin orange picking...
Picking oranges
Izumi Ward, Yokohama
Izumi Ward, Yokohama City.
Tantan Izumi Ward
It's Tan-Tan Izumi Ward.
After this, we'll sing a song like this.
Yes, that's right.
We did it, so just in time.
Yes, just in time.
The round koala from Izumi Ward.
Thank you very much.
Talented master.
Yes
Always a cute part-timer, Mr. Yamichiu
Hi
Yes, sir
Good evening. Good evening.
This is the last taste-hunting Kannonzaki in Yokosuka this year, isn't it?
I went mandarin orange picking.
So it was a beautiful day, and I was thirsty after moving around a bit.
So I enjoyed tangerines like juice from a drink bar.
Wow, I love it! As if to quench my thirst
Orange juice!
I heard that she has a daughter, and this year she will be able to pick a lot of her favorite mandarin oranges with scissors by herself
She is so excited because she can now pick her favorite mandarin oranges with scissors by herself!
She sent me a picture of her daughter at that time.
She sent me a picture of her daughter at that time, and it's very interesting.
She's trying to go just like that.
She's so funny! I love her so much!
I wonder what she's doing.
I'm going. Like that.
It's so cute.
I love it.
We're almost there.
It's too bad.
But maybe in another year we'll get it.
Can't you just get up and go?
This is a little on my knees.
Snap!
Like a bread-eating contest.
I see...
There's one more thing.
One more thing.
Shimaneko from Kanagawa Ward
Yokohama City
Thank you very much.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
I always enjoy watching you.
Thank you very much.
I'm retiring in December.
I'm retiring in December and going home.
Probably because you say Shimaneko.
Oh, you have a family home in Shimane?
I have only one month left to see the museum's devils!
Oh, no!
It was fun to see so many idols on this music-centered show!
Yeah...
It's the season when you can see Christmas trees all over the city
The mailbox at the post office in my neighborhood was also decorated with Christmas-style Santa Claus!
Phew!
So...
Here it is...
Here's what it looks like
Cute!
So cute!
Wow!
Maboroka.
So cute!
Shimaneko sent me a lot of pictures.
Can't we see them on tver or something?
That's right.
Well, if you're interested then...
I know Shimaneko's tver.
There's an app called tver.
Yes, there is.
Yes, it's there.
You can watch everything from Tuesday to Friday.
You can watch them all if you have a signal.
If you have a signal, you can watch it.
If you have a signal, you can watch it on TVer.
As a Shimane girl...
As a Shimane native, I'm sure you'll be able to find something about Shimane.
Please send me your Shimane stories.
Yes, and also...
This one's also good. He often sends me stories.
This person often sends me these, too.
He went to Kyoto... Kyoto... and in the cityscape of Kyoto...
I found a very austere store in the streets of Kyoto, so I went in.
First of all, this is what it looks like.
I think it's a restaurant.
It's amazing!
What kind of restaurant? I can't get enough of it.
There used to be a restaurant like this in the Showa period.
And these samples... wow!
There's an old one with a tarnished color...
I think this is the real thing.
The interior is also very austere.
This chair moves and rattles.
It rattles and rattles.
Yes, and then something...
And from the menu, there's this Italian hamburger steak.
550 yen. Cheap!
Onions, peppers, mushrooms, ham...
Lightly seasoned spaghetti with onions, green peppers, mushrooms, ham, etc.
And a hamburger steak with a nostalgic feel like a Marushin hamburger steak!
It's topped with a hamburger steak like a Marushin hamburger steak!
I love it, don't you?
It's delicious.
Looks so good!
I don't want this kind of old-fashioned diner or restaurant to disappear.
I don't want them to disappear.
No, it's true.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well...
By the way, what is your birthday, Warko?
Mine is October 28th.
October already?
I'm already 23 years old.
I wanted to give you the book around that time, but I didn't have a shift, so I'm giving it to you today.
I'm a little late, but yeah, yeah, I'd like to do it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the present.
Doraemon check... this is a lo I've seen before... what is it?
Gelapiquet red Gelapiquet!
Red Gelapiquet!
A bright red Gelapiquet.
Do you have any idol songs?
Thank you. That's great.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
What's so stylish already? It's so stylish.
The wrapping.
It's a little Christmasy.
I guess it's the time of year.
What is it?
I wonder...
what is it?
eh?
Uk.
what?
What?
It's cute.
What is it?
Don't worry.
Even Daiko
Rapid boku bum fuma-chan's swimming suit
Oh, I see
ah, ah, great, great, great, what is this? play is that Mariko's child actually this that you can carry in your cell before? datte yes, great, how many months old do you think she is?
No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, I don't.
I'm not here to visit you.
It's for Ukku only!
Oh, he's so cute! Thank you!
Eh, so cute!
Put Wook in here.
Put it in.
Let's load it up.
Let's put it in.
I can do it.
It's not a Gundam.
It's cool!
Put it in here.
We're gonna walk.
That's awesome!
Oh, yeah, it's so cute!
Amazing!
This will make Wook happy again.
This is awesome!
Thank you.
Amazing!
By the way...
I think this is something Wook would wear.
I think it's a hat...
By the way, Mariko, can I ask you to wear it?
It'll stretch your head.
It'll stretch.
I didn't know you could take it off.
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
Oh, that's nice.
That's so cute.
A reindeer.
You can be a reindeer?
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the samsishot.
Thank you. Thank you for being cute.
That's a lifesaver.
So cute.
It's cold when I go outside.
I'll put it on.
Wow!
It's great.
That's why...
Is it time to use the chopsticks?
So many devil's charges!
Happy Birthday
Happy birthday
mnagaoka
Happy Birthday Mariko
Thank you very much
99shiki
Thank you for Mariko's autographed photo book.
Thank you very much!
Kahikohiho
Congratulations to Mariko!
Thank you very much!
I hope this is okay.
It's amazing.
Cute.
I like it.
And many more comments.
Happy Birthday!
Thank you so much
Well, well, well, well.
That's why I'm here.
I'll see you next week with those chopsticks.
7:00 p.m.
Oh, my God.
Why?
It's on my schedule.
Oh, yeah.
7:00 p.m. I hope to see you all next week.
So, Mr. Nagashinoi, I'll see you one last time from here.
Like, "See you later.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work. See you next week.
A big smile.
See you later!
See you soon!